The kettle and the idol
Q. The second element is to let them be free. Are you having a bad day? Are you asking for advice?
This is a message, isn't it?
Who is this message to?
This is for everyone in the team,
I'm a free spirit who likes to take things at my own pace, so I don't like to be restrained.
I'm a free person and I like to take things at my own pace, so I don't like to be restrained,
I don't like to be restrained. I am always being told to know this or that.
I don't like to be told to change my clothes quickly,
So I try to change my clothes at my own pace a few minutes in advance as a result of what I have learned,
But the basic rule is to go at your own pace.
I would like to deliver this message to everyone in the team.
I think the fans know this, but I want to let them be free to do what they want,
I know that the fans are aware of this, but I want to let them have the same freedom as I have always had,
But when we have rehearsals and performances, there are times when we are not in the dressing room,
I am often not in the dressing room,
I would go out for a while.
And when I went outside, I noticed that the members were there,
What? Where did you go, Haru? I found a bakery and told them I bought some bread,
I found a bakery and said I bought some bread,
If there was a shopping street nearby, we would go to the shopping street,
I've been free to do whatever I want. I've been doing that up until now.
I've always been free to go anywhere,
Do they ever ask you to stop?
So far, no.So far, no.
But I guess that means I'm free.
I am free.
Even during live performances, you go off stage,
You take the initiative?
Yes, I do. I take the initiative,
Take the initiative?
I get excited,
When I went on stage just this year,
It was an event at an airport in Nagoya called Centria,
I got off the stage just before the MC was about to perform.
So I thought I could get off the stage,
So I thought I could get off the stage, and I was able to perform about five songs,
During the live performance of "Embracing Ansmu," one of the most popular songs at the concert, I was so excited that I got off the stage,
I was so excited that I wanted to get off the stage,
I had a part to play and I had to rap next,
I looked at the chief manager who was standing next to me,
I looked at the chief manager beside me and said, "Can you go? I looked at the chief manager beside me and said, "Can you go?
Didn't you notice that?
I was looking at him.
You gave him a look? He's just going down there by himself?
That's right.
I should have checked right before I went down, but I didn't.
But I think those of you who came to the meeting would have understood,
I'm sure some of you have memories of getting off the train,I think some of you have memories of how it was going down,
I didn't get a definite OK.
Because I sent it from my perspective?
I sent it from my perspective, so I thought, personally, they would probably have received it.
I got off.
They told me it was over.
It had been a long time. That look in your eyes.
Oh, oh.
The chief manager is quite revealing, isn't he?
Yes. I call her Popo-chan,
Popo-chan is much the same way.
Words are made up, aren't they?
Our live concert sounds interesting.
Please come and visit us.
I will.
Isn't it great?
I think it's more amazing than I can say.
I think it's great.
Isn't it great?
Courtesy of Mayu-san.
Summer means the ocean.
And when I say "ocean," I mean "tree.